// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q013: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Various driving tests are ------ in several countries for the practical implementation of automated driving.',
      choices: ['conducting', 'being conducted', 'conduct', 'conducts'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['conducted'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Greenleaf Gardening sells a ------ range of flower seeds in its store as well as online.',
      choices: ['broad', 'broaden', 'broadness', 'broadly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['broad'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'After working for three years at a financial institution in Hong Kong, Ms. Fujita ------ to Tokyo and established a financial consulting firm.',
      choices: ['arrived', 'visited', 'returned', 'reached'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['returned'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Due to a significant increase in employees this year, Peach Design Systems will need to move to a ------ larger office.',
      choices: ['very', 'quite', 'so', 'much'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['much'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Given that we were able to develop a competitive application, hiring several talented programmers was ------ a success.',
      choices: ['clear', 'clearly', 'clearing', 'clearness'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['clearly'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The Koizumi Municipal Library will be closed for renovations ------ on Wednesday, June 1.',
      choices: ['begin', 'will begin', 'beginning', 'have begun'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['beginning'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Entering the order number of an item into the tracking system will ------ users to track their packages.',
      choices: ['prevent', 'undergo', 'allow', 'approve'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['allow'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Tanaka was able to get a position as an accounting assistant that became available last week in a ------ manner.',
      choices: ['congested', 'periodical', 'timely', 'numerous'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['timely'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The social media product promotion organized by Mr. Stone has been one of the most successful advertising campaigns ------.',
      choices: ['soon', 'ago', 'still', 'ever'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['ever'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'MT Rental Company hired an ------ programmer to add new features to its meeting room reservation management system.',
      choices: ['experiencing', 'experience', 'experiences', 'experienced'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['experienced'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}